Okay. So, here we have um the use of
color alone which is not good uh for a
few reasons. One, screen reader users
don't aren't told what color the
background of a cell is in a table. Uh
and then there's also color blindness to
consider with red green looking like
identical to them. So in this table we
have a various tasks and a status with
just the status of of green, yellow or
red and then a legend which states that
done is green, in progress is yellow and
not started as is in red. So instead you
can simplify this and you can you can
keep the green uh as long as you meet
color contrast um requirements but you
can have for draft proposal um that
status level is done as is review
feedback is done and the finalized
budget is in progress
and for not uh for uh submit report is
uh it's red and is not started. So now
you have the visual plus you have the
actual meaning if it's done or in
progress or hasn't been started. And now
we can even delete this legend table
because it's no longer required.
Thank you.